Tomas Mozdren

mozdrent@gmail.com beangreen247.github.io

Seeking position in: Software Development

I am a somewhat capable developer with experience in programming everything from Web development to App development creating web apps and desktop applications. I am a solo programmer capable of working in a team or alone, depending on the task that was given.

Technical Skills:

Languages: C, C++, C#, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Python, Java

Frameworks: Microsoft .Net, Winforms, GTK

Tools: Visual Studios (2013, 2015, 2017, 2019, Code), Oracle SQL Developer, Notepad+++, Git,

GitHub, PuTTY, Bash, Powershell, CMD

Additional Experience: Windows, Ubuntu (Desktop, Server), Fedora, Arch, Debian, SUSE, Shell scripting

A little bit of robotics as well, like working with a raspbberry pi or devices similar to ir, used it various ways.

Work experience:

21/05/2018-01/06/2018 Assistant worker

Semperflex Optimit s.r.o., Odry (Czechia)

maintenance of computers

22/05/2017-02/06/2017 Assistant worker

Semperflex Optimit s.r.o., Odry (Czechia)

maintenance of computers

Education:

06/09/2015-30/06/2021 School leaving exam Maturita EQF level 4

Gymnázium a Střední průmyslová škola elektrotechniky a informatiky, Frenštát pod Radhoštěm, příspěvková organizace, Frenštát pod Radhoštěm (Czechia)

- Programming
- Databases
- Measurements and diagnostics
- Electronics
- Networking
- Telecommunications

Personal Projects:

- I make videos about software development and technology on YouTube, you can view it here. (https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCQbA5Nc4oq6uMS2idDWsxkw)
- UraniumNote, a web app written in JavaScript for taking notes, that can be accessed here.
 (https://beangreen247.github.io/UraniumNote)
- **UraniumWebTerm**, a web app written in JavaScript simulating an online terminal, that can be accessed <u>here</u>.

(https://beangreen247.github.io/UraniumWebTerm)

• **Minimalist chatbot**, a web app written in JavaScript, a chat-bot that interacts with the user using predefined commands, that can be accessed <u>here</u>.

(https://beangreen247.github.io/Minimalist-chatbot)

• **Python-AI-Arts**, AI written in Python using the Keras and Tensorflow library, repository can be found here.

(https://github.com/BeanGreen247/Python-AI-Arts)

• **Object-detection-using-Tensorflow**, object detection in Python using the Tensorflow library, repository can be found here.

(https://github.com/BeanGreen247/Object-detection-using-Tensorflow)

Released software:

• Windows 10 Minimizer, a utility to make your Windows 10 install more lightweight. Written in C#, repository can be found here.

(https://github.com/BeanGreen247/Windows-10-Minimizer)

• **Image To ASCII Converter,** a utility to convert an image to ASCII art. Written in C#, repository can be found <u>here</u>.

(https://github.com/BeanGreen247/ImageToASCIIConverter)